<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Hello Friend</title>
    
    
    
    <link>https://ahmedameenaim.github.io/ahmedamin.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Hello Friend</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 27 Jun 2021 00:53:51 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://ahmedameenaim.github.io/ahmedamin.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Containers attacks - ways of escape container</title>
      <link>https://ahmedameenaim.github.io/ahmedamin.github.io/posts/post3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Jun 2021 00:53:51 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ahmedameenaim.github.io/ahmedamin.github.io/posts/post3/</guid>
      <description>
        
          &lt;img src=&#34;https://ahmedameenaim.github.io/ahmedamin.github.io/amcO9glU.jpg&#34;/&gt;
          
        
        
        
          This post is I&amp;rsquo;m talking about container security topic , it&amp;rsquo;s demonstrate how a vulnerable application in dockerize environment can be critical catastrophic to enterprises.
Introduction Container technology has radically changed the way that applications are being developed and deployed. Notably, containers dramatically ease dependency management, so shipping new features or code is faster than ever before. While Docker containers and Kubernetes are great for DevOps, they also present new security challenges that both security practitioners and developers must understand and address with diligence.
          
        
        </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Istio Security (securing microservices traffic with istio)</title>
      <link>https://ahmedameenaim.github.io/ahmedamin.github.io/posts/post2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Jun 2021 19:28:29 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ahmedameenaim.github.io/ahmedamin.github.io/posts/post2/</guid>
      <description>
        
          &lt;img src=&#34;https://ahmedameenaim.github.io/ahmedamin.github.io/istio-cover.png&#34;/&gt;
          
        
        
        
          In this post I&amp;rsquo;m gonna talking about how to secure your micro-services in service mesh using istio. Prefer if the reader have a foundation knowledge of kubernetes but it&amp;rsquo;s not mandatory at all.
So What is Istio ? Istio is a service mesh that allows organizations to connect, secure and observe microservices. Since its inception three years ago, it’s risen to become one of Google’s most prominent open source projects, a top-three keyword at KubeCon, and a mature, production-ready offering supported by a robust community.
          
        
        </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>https://ahmedameenaim.github.io/ahmedamin.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ahmedameenaim.github.io/ahmedamin.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
          
          
        
        
        
          Hi there My name is Ahmed Amin and I&amp;rsquo;m the fastest man alive :D
I Am working as a product security engineer at Swvl. I have made this blog for educational purposes. This blog will go into many security topics like offensive attacks, defending, coding challenges and much more cool stuff. it will be a great opportunity to contribute with me to learn from each other within this blog. Hope to get your attention and to be a good resource for anyone who wants to learn.
          
        
        </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Browny Machine Writeup (easy)</title>
      <link>https://ahmedameenaim.github.io/ahmedamin.github.io/posts/writeup1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2019 01:12:17 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ahmedameenaim.github.io/ahmedamin.github.io/posts/writeup1/</guid>
      <description>
        
          &lt;img src=&#34;https://ahmedameenaim.github.io/ahmedamin.github.io/cover.jpg&#34;/&gt;
          
        
        
        
          ======================
Hey guys , today I will walkthrough step by step in Browny Machine. this Machine is so good for beginner in pentration testing you will gonna learn a lot in this experenice. It is an easy linux machine , We will exploit Xplico Remote Code Execution in a vulnerable version Xplico that listen on port 9876 by default. There is a hidden end-point at inside of the Xplico that allow anyone to create a new user that can execute a terminal command under the context of the root user.
          
        
        </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://ahmedameenaim.github.io/ahmedamin.github.io/showcase/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ahmedameenaim.github.io/ahmedamin.github.io/showcase/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
          
          
        
        
        
          Under Construction 
          
        
        </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>